Warwick Hart

www.warwickhart.com

contact@warwickhart.com | +44 7926 274 899 | Brighton, UK





Summary

Give me a problem and I will dedicate myself to understanding the cause and finding the optimal solution. Over many years I have self-taught myself coding but in 2022 I decided to finally get an official certification in full stack development. I took the initiative and signed up to a 12-month coding course and I have been able to take my base line knowledge to a whole new level. I invite you to take a moment to review my portfolio and I look forward to speaking to you soon.

Technical Skillset

I am currently familiar with the following languages and technologies but pick up new ones fast, as I am adapted to self-learning.

HTML | CSS | JavaScript | Python | Lua | VBA | MySQL | GitHub | GitPod |

Portfolio

The best way to see my portfolio, the repositories and the live sites is visiting my website.

Why Choose Popcorn? HTML | CSS | GitHub | Fictional website built as my first project. The website is designed to demonstrate using HTML and CSS to create a fully responsive website regardless the screen size (down to 320px width that is!).

Random Result Generator HTML | CSS | JavaScript | GitHub | If you are looking for a Random Result Generator? Then look no further! Originally created as a project for my diploma, once the final assessment is done, I plan to come back and make this project shine even more.

Hotdog Empire Tycoon Python | API | GitHub | Heroku | A fun game about trying to create a hotdog empire within 10 days (20 game cycles in total). It is created using Python and currently deployed on Heroku. It uses an API with Google to store game data and a features a fully functioning leaderboard.

WARWICK HART.developer (); HTML | CSS | JavaScript | GitHub | My portfolio website. The purpose of the website is to showcase my portfolio and to be a one stop shop of finding all relevant information about me as a developer.

Other Projects

Here are some projects that I have done in the past and are not available for you to physically see but to give you an idea of other previous experience in coding.

International Medical Insurance Sales Quote Tool Excel | VBA | HTML | While working for Bupa we used an old quote system that was terribly slow. To help improve productivity and provide a better customer experience. I solely created a new sales quote took that is now used in

the UK and Ireland (for EU). It provides instant quotes which are then exported into an email template to be sent to the customer, saving hours of work time each week.

GTA V online & Read Dead Redemption online Lua | HTML | CSS | JavaScript | As a little passion to feed my need to solve problems and write code. I assist with different groups of people to help write scripts for mods and help them solve coding problems when they are unable to figure out the solution themselves.

Certifications

In progress. **Full stack developer diploma** with Code Institute.

5-day coding challenge with Code Institute.

Leadership & Management Diploma with Corndel.

Principles of Management and Leadership, Level 3 with Charted Management Institute.

Team leader or supervisor, Level 3 with Institute for Apprenticeships & Technical Education,

Certificate in Financial Advice (CeFA) 1 and Certificate in Financial Advice (CeFA) 6.

Education

Varndean College, September 2004 until July 2006.

Dorothy Stringer High School, September 2002 until July 2004.

Falmer High School, September 1999 until July 2002.

Qualifications

A2 qualifications in Computing, photography, and mathematics.

AS qualifications in Computing, ICT, and electronics.

GNVQ qualifications in ICT, Numerical modelling using spreadsheets; Presenting information; Handling information; Graphics and desktop publishing; Information technology.

GCSE qualifications C grade and above in English, mathematics, double science, electronics, and 6 other GCSE qualifications.

Professional Experience

Direct Sales Adviser, Bupa Global, January 2017 to Present.

Branch Manager, Post Office Ltd, December 2015 to December 2016.

Branch Manager, Sequence Ltd, February 2012 to November 2015.

Mortgage Advisor, Sequence Ltd, January 2011 to January 2012.

Sales Supervisor, Sony Centre, August 2008 to December 2010.

Sales Advisor, Comet Plc, October 2006 to July 2008.